[
    {
        "question": "Fiets",
        "options": [ "Car", "Bus", "Bicycle", "Boat" ],
        "answer": "Bicycle"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tussendoortje",
        "options": [ "Snack", "Interview", "Exam", "Traffic Jam" ],
        "answer": "Snack"
    },
    {
        "question": "Regenboog",
        "options": [ "Rainbow", "Sun", "Cloud", "Storm" ],
        "answer": "Rainbow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Schaap",
        "options": [ "Cow", "Sheep", "Goat", "Pig" ],
        "answer": "Sheep"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gebouw",
        "options": [ "Building", "Field", "Car", "House" ],
        "answer": "Building"
    },
    {
        "question": "Appel",
        "options": [ "Orange", "Banana", "Apple", "Pear" ],
        "answer": "Apple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Zon",
        "options": [ "Moon", "Star", "Sun", "Planet" ],
        "answer": "Sun"
    },
    {
        "question": "Boom",
        "options": [ "Flower", "Tree", "Leaf", "Grass" ],
        "answer": "Tree"
    },
    {
        "question": "Koffie",
        "options": [ "Tea", "Water", "Coffee", "Juice" ],
        "answer": "Coffee"
    },
    {
        "question": "Zuster",
        "options": [ "Aunt", "Sister", "Niece", "Cousin" ],
        "answer": "Sister"
    }
]